Andre Rafael Freitas Ferreira



E-mail: andrerafaelff@gmail.com

Website:

https://andrerafaelf.github.io/andrerfferreira-

portfolio/

Phone: 926652761

INTERESTS

A high achiever committed to exceeding targets, with excellent team leading skills as well as a good team player. I can demonstrate key social skills and have the ability to communicate effectively with a diverse audience. I am excellent at building relationships, outgoing, reliable, ambitious and always willing to learn and take responsibility. I can use initiative to focus and create quality solutions to problems. I enjoy new challenges, have good time management skills and am dedicated in all that I do.

After 2 years studying in Lisbon I decided to move abroad to pursue a career in Web Development, a career in which I'd imagined myself being in since I was a kid.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Civil Service Club, London

Sep 2017 - Jun 2019

Food and Beverage Assistant

- Looking after two sites delivering hospitality and events in each.
- Working alongside the duty manager to ensure all team Leaders & Host/ Hostess are completing daily and weekly
- jobs.
- Great communication with all staff and FOH.
- Dealing with complains in a professional manner.
- Delivering excellent customer service.
- Purchase of special dietary request for customers.
- Be aware of health, safety and fire procedures, and assume responsibility for the safety of work area. Cash and till
- handling behind the bar.
- Stock take and stock management.
- End of the day banking.
- Receive, order and serve customer requests.
- Taking part in serveral courses (First aid, Cellar management)

Sejuiced Ltd. London Aug 2019 - Feb 2020

Kitchen and Events manager

- Looking after two sites The kitchen when making drinks or insuring drinks are being made according to health and
- safety measures at event sites.
- Working alongside the manager to ensure customers were always up to date with amounts of drinks sold and
- amounts left to be made .
- Great communication with all staff at events and at office kitchen.

Andre Rafael Freitas Ferreira

- Delivering excellent customer service.
- Be aware of health, safety and fire procedures, and assume responsibility for the safety of work area.ent.
- Driving to and from events and making sure events are set-up accordingl

ASDA Stores Ltd. London

Security Guard

- Counting customers in accordance with COVID-19 measures.
- Dealing with queues outside the store to maintain a low amount of customers inside the store.
- Obersving high value stock in store.
- Dealing with complaints in a professional manner.
- De-escalating aggressive situations.

EDUCATION

Linguas, Literaturas & Culturas

Faculdade de Letras da Universidade de Lisboa

Sep 2016 - Sep 2018

Sep 2020 - Jan 2022

Diploma in Full Stack Web Development

Mar 2021 - Fev 2022

Code Institute

Code Institute is an**online coding bootcamp**offering a FullStack Software Development diploma. The Full Stack Software Development curriculum covers HTML, CSS, Python, Django, JavaScript, and competencies such as agile development and projectmanagement.

QUALIFICATIONS

- HTML5
- CSS3
- JavaScript
- Python
- 1. Bootstrap
- 2. jQuery
- 3. Flask
- 4. Django

REFERENCES

References available upon request.

Andre Rafael Freitas Ferreira 2